Lingguo Temple.
I want you to go to the Empress
and ask the Emperor for an imperial edict.
Imperial edict?
Now the Second Prince hates me to the bone.
I can't stay at Prince Rui's Mansion for long.
I need to find a way to get out of here.
In a few days,
I will make a risky move.
It may alarm the palace
[and may upset Consort Ling]
[and even His Majesty.]
[At that time,]
[I need Your Majesty to intervene]
[and persuade His Majesty]
[to send me to Lingguo Temple.]
We've come full circle back here.
Let's go.
You mentioned that Princess Consort Rui knew the Imperial Consort Dowager,
and now she's been sent to Lingguo Temple.
It's probably not a coincidence, right?
I once asked my mother.
She clearly doesn't know Shen Suhe at all.
How does Shen Suhe
know about my mother?
We should increase the guard
of my mother's yard.
As for Shen Suhe,
the Second Prince won't give up.
Wait for a while before taking action.
Miss, slow down.
Slow down.
This is the room arranged for you by the abbot.
It's different from the mansion.
Please bear with it.
Although it looks simple,
everything you need is here.
Thank you for your consideration.
I appreciate it.
I'm Wu Xin.
If you need anything,
you can come to me in the front yard.
Miss, you are badly hurt,
and you have to live in such a place.
They are really too much.
It's okay.
It's better than losing your life in the mansion.
Go.
Find some water.
Let's wash up.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You're hurt.
Let me pull it out for you.
Don't worry about me.
Take care of your own injuries.
All settled.
Two got away.
We've sent someone to chase them.
Their target is clear,
it's Mu Jinghao's men.
Remember to apply medicine.
Mr.
Wang.
He got shot.
The arrow is poisonous.
Poisonous?
You're awake, Miss.
You've been sleeping for a day and night.
A day and night?
Be careful, Miss.
You're still injured.
Does it hurt?
Right.
Why don't I feel any pain?
That gentleman didn't lie to me.
What gentleman?
It's
the people who saved you that night.
Two of them look familiar.
They seem to be the same two people
you met on the day you escaped the marriage.
Where are they?
In the yard.
Miss,
have you
recovered from the poison?
Do you think everyone is like you,
stubbornly enduring punishment?
You...
blocked the poisoned arrow for me
and gave me medicine.
I owe you,
and I'll repay you when I have the chance.
Why are you in Lingguo Temple?
How can I find you?
Did you know you would be expelled here?
Or did you plan it step by step?
The process is not important.
What matters is that I'm here.
And Consort Dowager Li is also here.
What I told you before
about Consort Dowager Li
is all true.
I'll figure it out.
But
you seem to owe me an explanation.
I want to see my brother first.
Okay.
At night,
I'll bring him to see you.
Miss,
go in and eat something.
Zhiyan,
go and find out secretly
the nuns who can come in and out of the temple freely.
Find two or three reliable ones
and bring them to me.
Okay.
I'll go right away.
Please.
Thank you.
Brother.
It's really you.
How is father?
I asked you to come today
to save father.
Who is that man?
Have you really investigated him?
Don't worry.
He is reliable.
And
I have become an enemy
with the Second Prince.
He is the real culprit who framed father.
Mu Jinghao, the bastard.
Now the Prime Minister's Mansion is ruined.
and my father's former colleagues are all avoiding him,
refusing to lend a hand.
I know you never liked court struggles,
so you sought a position in the Hanlin Academy.
But compared to me,
my father had more interactions with you.
If you recall any clues,
you must tell me.
Actually, over the years,
I've just feigned indifference in the Hanlin Academy.
maintaining a neutral stance in the court.
But secretly,
I have been helping my father investigate
the evidence of the Second Prince's crimes.
He has been threatening and bribing people,
forming cliques for personal gain.
If we can present these to Your Majesty,
maybe
we can save my father's life for the time being.
So my father knew about the Second Prince's evil deeds long ago.
Then why did he...
Why
to marry Prince Rui?
Father was forced to do so.
His Majesty has made up his mind.
If father refuses,
he will be stripped of his position.
You know father.
He is not a power-hungry person.
He just can't watch the Second Prince
continue to cause chaos in the imperial court.
You don't need to say more.
No matter how wrong father is,
now is not the time to dwell on right or wrong.
The most important thing now
is to clear father's
and the Prime Minister's Residence's
name.
The man at the door,
Young Master Lou,
what's wrong with him?
Although I haven't interacted much with him,
I can
sense he is no ordinary person.
Maybe he can meet my father.
Before that,
we have found a lot of
evidence against the Second Prince.
Except for those destroyed by him on the day of confiscation,
there are some more important ones
hidden away.
As for where they are hidden,
only my father knows.
Only my father knows.
I want to see my father.
To break into the prison,
can you do it?
You,
a weak woman with no strength.
I can.
Of course,
with you.
Alright.
But the smoke won't last long,
so we need to hurry.
Which one?
According to my investigation during the day,
the one in the farthest.
Let's go.
Father.
Hurry up.
Sui'er.
Sui'er!
Wake up, Sui'er!
Go get the doctor!
Yes.
Sui'er!
It's okay.
Why did you take the arrow for me?
You once blocked one for me,
so I just
paid you back.
You're so reckless.
It's okay.
I'm quite lucky.
I just don't want to owe
anyone anything.
Sui'er,
I saved your life first.
Even if you want to die,
you have to ask my permission.
Sui'er.
Don't sleep.
Your Highness is wise.
You moved Shen Yi in advance,
so the rebel failed.
What you should consider is
what kind of force this is.
who broke into the prison and got away.
What do you think, Your Highness?
What do I think?
Search the whole city now!
Yes, sir.
Your Highness,
the new taro powder
has been successfully developed.
Since someone is helping the PM,
I'll destroy them faster and more thoroughly.
Shen Suhe,
let's start with you.
How is she?
She has been in fever for a day and night.
Will she...
Miss,
I can't...
Can you get some ice?
Ice?
What are you doing?
It seems to work.
Leave her to me.
You...
Don't worry.
I won't do anything to her.
I don't mean that.
I'll go make the medicine.
Don't leave me.
Don't.
Don't worry.
I'm here.
Do you feel better?
I'm a little hot.